Welcome back. Have a look.
it's time for the dark theater.
Willow Chest
This is, the story of a family living a hard life.
Are you really going to sell that?
I can't help it.
That's the only way.
Otherwise, I can't buy rice for tomorrow.
Mom,
I'm hungry.
We have to sell it.
Udajii.
Udajii/Old Uda (うだじい): A localized term for a protector spirit that inhabits the family's traditional willow chest.
But, it's something precious that you brought,
when got married, isn't it?
it's okay.
But...
I...
I want to go back to my parents' home for Obon festival this year.
i wonder if dad's doing well.
I haven't been home in a year.
Alright.
Then...let's go.
i miss the river i used to play in when i was a kid.
I want to go back to that time.
Mom is talking to Old Uda again.
Old Uda,
That’s all for today.
When I'm with Old Uda,
Mom looks happy when she's with Old Uda.
Old Uda,
I also have a favor to ask.
Does it have to be Mom?
Tomorrow, I will get married.
Tae-san
You've decided well.
Thank you.
I've already decided.
i'm sorry!
Are you really sure it's okay to sell old Uda?
I'm sorry!
Something terrible is happening!
I'm off.
Have a nice day.
Why are you bringing it back?
It can't be helped.
It didn't sell.
Did you go around?
I did my best.
but it didn't work.
I'm hungry.
This was for the best.
Otherwise,
it would have turned into a disaster.
Misfortune would come to us.
Please continue to protect us.
Old Uda.
The END